[Music]
this morning mg PLC began trading on the
London Stock Exchange marking the
successful completion of its two merger
from the Prudential Group this is one of
the most significant changes in the long
history of our business I would like to
wish our friends at mg the very best on
their journey as an independent company
they have excellent opportunities and a
high quality management team and I have
no doubt they have a bright future
we do a great job for customers and
they'll see no change in the services we
provide which makes such a positive
difference in their lives
but the demerger will enable us to do a
better job in two important ways first
it will make us more aligned more
closely in step with the interests of
our key stakeholders second it'll make
us more focused we can focus more on
improving our businesses and we will be
able to allocate resources our time our
people in our capital even more
effectively
we've been serving customers for more
than 170 years and all that time our
underlying purpose as a business that is
the reason we exist hasn't changed
put simply we help de-risk life's big
financial concerns and we make people's
hard-earned savings go further by
putting that money to work we have an
important role to play and the key
moments in people's lives that means big
events like an episode of ill-health the
birth of a child or the approach of
retirement we ease our customers
anxieties and help them plan for the
future with confidence that purpose
continues to guide our strategic
thinking how we develop propositions for
our customers and how we create value
for our shareholders
we're an Asian LED group Asia has the
greatest unmet need for what we do and
we have leadership positions in the
region which give us options a few of
our competitors have and Asia is where
we see the fastest growing demand for
our services the vast majority of people
entering the global middle class are
agents and these families have an urgent
need to save more and protect themselves
against ill health in the United States
or other major market Americans are
getting older and they have an equally
strong demand for greater financial
security in their retirement our
well-established Asian and US businesses
are truly leaders in their fields and we
believe our African businesses will also
be champions of the future we focus on
creating long-term shareholder value
that means creating trusted
relationships with our customers which
translate into high-quality and
recurring earnings this is a strategy
that supports increased investment for
future profitable growth and delivers
progressive dividends for our
shareholders but being a world-class
group does not mean we should be
everywhere or own everything we invest
for long-term profitable growth and
we've never been afraid of exiting
businesses that don't fit with our
strategy this active approach will
continue
we're a highly innovative business we've
just launched a unique digital health
service that's winning praise from both
policymakers and medical professionals
we've made large elements of the
customer journey digital and in some of
our markets were close to a hundred
percent digital and and at the same time
we're building new distribution channels
so that more customers than ever have
access to our services what's the aim of
this innovation it's simple more
customers deeper customer experiences
and even stronger customer loyalty and
more value for shareholders
our culture embraces change and is
underpinned by our core behaviors first
ownership the belief that people should
be empowered to take decisions and be
accountable for those decisions
second is partnership successful
collaboration is key to our business
both within our organization and with
third parties third would be stewardship
we should leave our business and our
communities stronger than when we found
them
we provide solutions to some of the
biggest challenges facing the world too
few people enjoy good health care or the
benefit of financial protection and
savings we're increasing access to both
at the same time the world is growing
older placing financial pressure on
families and societies we're bringing
new retirement solutions to the places
where these demographic shifts are
happening fastest and developing
economies need investment in jobs and
infrastructure we're channeling more and
more of our customer savings into
industries that power long-term
prosperity that's how we fulfill our
purpose and then demerger now behind us
we're entering a new phase we'll
continue to innovate to create solutions
for our customers and continue to work
to unlock value for our investors
[Music]